{
    "id": "99265e29d20543499fc441dce8107960",
    "title": "Word Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We took a ……………………. path.",
            "description": "Circuitous means devious or roundabout.",
            "answers": [
                "circuit",
                "circuitous",
                "circumvent"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The …………………………. motion of the merry go round made the girl dizzy.",
            "description": "Circular means twirling, revolving or spinning.",
            "answers": [
                "circular",
                "circling",
                "circle"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Her moods are as …………………………. as the weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "change",
                "changeable",
                "changing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy attended school only under ………………………..",
            "description": "Coercion means compulsion.",
            "answers": [
                "coerce",
                "coercion",
                "coercive"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If the team makes a ……………………… effort we will win the game.",
            "description": "Collective means unified.",
            "answers": [
                "collection",
                "collective",
                "collected"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The witness was remarkably ………………………… under the cross-examination.",
            "description": "Collected means self-controlled.",
            "answers": [
                "collection",
                "collected",
                "collective"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The diplomat was arrested for acting in ……………………….. with the enemy.",
            "description": "Collusion means secret agreement.",
            "answers": [
                "collision",
                "collusion"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The policemen …………………………… a taxi to chase the robbers.",
            "description": "Commandeered means seized or usurped.",
            "answers": [
                "commandered",
                "commanded",
                "commandeered"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He wanted to make his living in the arts rather than in the …………………………… world.",
            "description": "Commercial means related to business or trade.",
            "answers": [
                "commerce",
                "commercial"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was known for his …………………………… approach to life.",
            "description": "Commonsense means practical.",
            "answers": [
                "commonsense",
                "common sense",
                "commonplace"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This letter is not very …………………………..",
            "description": "Communicative means informative.",
            "answers": [
                "communicative",
                "communicable",
                "communication"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Being granted a yearly bonus can be considered ……………………….. to getting a raise.",
            "description": "Comparable can mean similar. Comparative means by comparison.",
            "answers": [
                "comparable",
                "comparative",
                "comparison"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}